Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Tim
Dylan Show. Uh, good to be with you as
always and I'm happy that you are here
with me. I hope I have your trust
because I I see trust being
uh removed from lots of people and for
good reason
because we are going to now I'm going to
tell you about a dinner I had with a a
member of the administration. I'm going
to tell you everything
that I know
and I'm going to say the things that I
do not know
and I am also not going to
um
attest to the veracity. Google it of the
information,
how true or false the information is.
I'm going to tell you what I was told.
Okay. It's not a defense of Trump. It's
not a defense of the administration. In
fact, I think if they do not release
everything they have, they are done. I
believe that
if they do not rel and I told them that
you need to release everything you have,
Pam Bondi needs to be fired.
I told them that. They know that. The
people I spoke to, person people person
people,
they know that
I went to Washington. We had a dinner as
a small dinner.
What day did I When did I go?
>> Uh, Wednesday.
>> I went Wednesday.
Here's the rub.
Jeffrey Epstein is an innocent man. I'm
kidding. That's not the rap. That's not
the rep.
Yes, it's a blackmail operation. Yes, it
was. Yes, this guy's got connections to
intelligence. Everybody knows that. Yes,
the intelligence is MSAD and CIA. Most
likely. We all know that.
Yes, he was he was running some type of
blackmail operation procuring young
girls for powerful people.
A lot of this was on tape
somewhere.
Um, when Pam Bondi came out and said, "I
have 10,000 hours of
evidence." What has been told to me
is that that is porn Epstein downloaded
from the internet. It is not the tapes
of powerful people in compromising
positions. And the PE and the person who
told me that said, "Listen, I'm not
saying those tapes don't exist. I'm
saying that it the person who has that
those tapes is either a foreign
intelligence service
Ireland
is a guess or a billionaire or
billionaires
or they have been destroyed."
You know, there isn't a tape of Bill
Clinton [__] a 12-year-old that Pam
Bondi has on her desk. She has
commercial pornography
downloaded from the internet. The tapes
that show incriminating things
are with who's ever blackmailing these
people. Again, this is what was told to
me.
And that which again
from the outside I can see whoever is
running this operation not being dumb
enough to let tapes
uh get to the desk of Pam Bondi who's
the attorney general. Now again do I
know what is on those tapes? Absolutely
not. I really don't want to know. I'm I
don't want a trove of uh pornography
delivered so I can analyze it. What was
told to me was that those tapes are
pornography,
some legal, some probably not, that he
had downloaded. There are tapes of
Epstein
walking around his house and there are
photos of underage girls, but there is
no tape of Bill Gates or Donald Trump or
Bill Clinton engaging in activity with a
minor.
Okay. However,
again, this is told to me at a at a
private dinner that we're having. I'm
not going to tell you who it's with. I
won't. If you're smart, maybe you know
by the end of the episode, but I don't
know if you're smart.
I don't know if you're smart. I'll drop
clues.
I'll drop little clues. I'll drop tiny
I'll drop tiny clues.
But I'm not going to tell you.
People speak, I think, under the
condition of some type of anonymity
here. Truly, no offense.
So, I'm not going to go out and say who
it was. I'm not going to say who it was.
Tiny clues. Tiny little clues.
And it wasn't RFK. I couldn't I couldn't
do that for an hour or two dinner. Can
you imagine that? I imagine
and I I couldn't I couldn't do it.
That's not who it was.
They know they have a problem. They got
a big problem.
You have to I don't think the grand jury
docks, which I also said you got to
unseal all of that. You got to get Bondi
to go to a judge and unseal it. That
will not
satiate people. You need to release all
of the documents
unless you're going to have a big
problem.
Trump and Epstein were friends for a
very long time. The nature of their
relationship
is kind of a mystery to a lot of people.
Donald Trump has said, "Hey, I knew the
guy. He traveled in society circles, New
York, Palm Beach."
Epstein said, "This guy was my best
friend." I think at one point I think
Trump and Epstein fell out over a house
they both wanted to buy. I know that
Epstein hit on a young girl at Mara Lago
and Trump kicked him out.
I don't know where they hung out, what
trips they took. I'm unaware of that.
People got mad at me on the la on the
last episode. They're like, "You're
covering for Trump." Uh and I'm like,
"I'm not covering for Trump."
Trump has never been accused of anything
with an underage person.
You know, he's clearly a guy that's
driven, like a lot of people, by sex,
and he's clearly somebody that
has probably acted inappropriately.
Um, but it was never he was never
accused of being with somebody who's
underage. And I think a lot of people
that don't like Trump would tell you
that wasn't his thing. A lot of these
women he was with, Ivana, Mara Maples,
are kind of like Vegas show girls. They
look like 35. Even when they're 25, a
lot of them, they're just caked in
makeup, huge hair, tits out, they're in
like a gold, you know? I mean, now is it
is it impossible that that uh that
Epstein or or whoever has some
compromising material on Trump?
Absolutely not. I don't know. But I I
only suggested that thus far that is not
something he's been accused of doing.
Okay, that doesn't mean that it it's
impossible. It's obviously not
impossible.
And in order to get this type of
speculation
to quiet down, they have to release
everything that they have. And I told
this person that
and this person knows that.
And we also discussed
chislain. Galileain.
Gileain. I think it's Gileain.
No one offered Galain a plea deal.
Nobody went to Gileain Maxwell and said,
"Give up
somebody and we will reduce your
sentence."
And that could be for a couple of
reasons. They didn't want to give a plea
deal to a pedophile. That's certainly
not a popular thing to do.
But it could also be because people
didn't want Galain
to belong. Actually, I have a funny
story. People didn't want that. They
weren't looking forward to that. They
said, "Keep your trap shut."
Now, I said at this dinner, I said,
"Gain must speak.
She should testify before Congress.
Couple of the people at the dinner,
again, it was a small dinner, three or
four people, about four people. Three,
four then three.
They knew.
They said that is not on the table at
the moment,
but it's not impossible.
Nobody's super jazzed about it.
Like it's been suggested.
Like I thought I had the idea first.
It I didn't. Other people had suggested
it. Why don't we get this [__] We know
where this [__] is.
We know where she is. Let's get her.
Let's put her under oath.
Let's have her raise the right hand and
let's have her talk about what this
operation was.
That has not been warmly received
by anybody over there. right, left,
center.
A lot of people in Washington
were not excited and probably New York,
Palm Beach, London,
any city you can't afford.
People weren't jazzed about that. They
weren't pumped up about her testifying.
You know how you meet your friend and
they're pumped up? They're running a a
5K and they're pumped up and they're
excited about it and they're telling
everyone they know about I'm I'm doing a
5K. Yeah, it's good to see you. I got to
keep running. I'm training for a 5K. And
they're pumped up and they're excited
and they keep talking about this thing
they're doing to keep pumping. This is
the opposite of that.
Just Maxwell testifying in front of
Congress. Kind of the opposite of that.
No one's running through the streets
going, "Let's get her to testify. Won't
it be fun?" That's not happening.
It's not exciting to a lot of people.
They have not embraced it. I think it's
a good idea. I told the people at the
dinner that they kind of agreed.
They get it. Put her under oath. Put her
in the chair.
The problem is she's going to want
something to testify and now you're
cutting the sentence of a pedophile.
Now what if she cuz Jizlain's an asset.
She's an intelligence asset. She's
probably not going to hang people with
the testimony.
She knows how to do that. She knows how
to say things without saying things. I'm
guessing I would imagine unless she just
decides to just [__] burn it all
down, but she probably won't.
Her dad, you know, I think a team of
people stormed this yacht, threw him
off.
You know, four Israeli prime ministers
were at his funeral. Hopefully, they'll
be at mine as well for different
reasons.
But
the heads of the MSAD, he got a great
uh, you know, a great burial plot in
Israel. Like, it's his whole thing. They
literally said he's done more for
Israel. Things we can't even say right
now. He was a big asset.
And and I think Galain values that.
That's dad. That's her daddy.
That's dad. You got to love your dad. Me
and my father don't have the greatest
relationship. I still love my dad.
I like things about my father. I like
that he does things like that. I do. He
looks down on people that are not that
lower than him. Almost not lower than
him. But I like that about him. He looks
way down on people that are not that
much lower than him. And I do as well. I
judge severely the people who are not
that much lower than me. And in fact, I
judge severely people that have things I
don't have and that are good. But I I
love that about my father. I like that
my father,
like I do, appropriates the
accomplishments of other people. Like,
you know, he will take pride in a in a
beautiful wealthy area or a skyscraper
or uh something that he had nothing to
do with. And I do the same thing. I I
like it and I talk about it like I had
something to do with it, but I didn't,
you know, and that's something I learned
from my father. You take pride in in
being near success.
My whole life I've done. I got
successful when I was like 40,
you know, 37, whatever. But like
before that, I took a lot of pride that
I was near success. I learned that from
my father. Be near success. Live near
success and then show people, look at
these [__] and how well they've done.
Show them that your bum friends are
going to come visit you. Show them the
people that have done it. And you take a
little bit from that and you make it
your own. You internalize it. You got to
love your dad. And her dad, say what you
want about him, but he was a super spy.
The guy did it. He was a media mogul. He
was a an access agent. He He was
working. The guy was working.
That's her father. I don't think she's
going to light it all on fire.
I think she values that. I think she
goes down with the ship.
And but then you know so the problem is
if she gets up there and she doesn't
really give people what they want. She's
not giving people up. Then you got to
pardon her. You got to pardon a a
pedophile.
That's a tough call. Everyone who visits
me on the private island I call home
tells me that the beds are the things
they remember. And the beds are all from
Helix. Helix is the greatest way to buy
a mattress. It is the best bed on the
market and the easiest to obtain. Okay.
You sleep better, you lose weight, you
gain weight, whatever you want. It helps
with everything. The apneas, the
problems to the you sleep to the left or
to the right or in the center. I love
Helix. You fill out a short quiz. They
tell you what kind of sleeper you are
and what kind of mattress they think
would work for you. I'm telling you,
everybody loves it. I like the Midnight
Deluxe, but other people like other
things. Go to helixleep.com/timd.
Okay, they're still doing the Fourth of
July sale. How cool is that? 27% off
sitewide. 27% off sitewide.
Helixleep.com/timd
helixleep.com/timd
and 27% off sitewide. The best beds on
the market. They are amazing.
Helixleep.com.
traffic yourself to your bed.
But supposedly they do not have tapes
that have incriminating
stuff. They have incriminating for the
man who's dead
or who's living in Les Wexner's house.
Get up Les Wexner's house. Get up how
big it is in New Albany, Ohio.
Is this man living? Was Jeffrey Epstein
switched out in the middle of the night?
And is he living
in Les Wexter's house?
Is he living there?
Couldn't he live there?
Wouldn't he be able to live there?
We don't know. I have info, folks. I can
say I want to say things here.
the guy who had less the guy who had
Epstein's job after Wexner. And I want
you to go find this. I don't know if you
can find it, but the guy who had
Epstein's job after Wexner
was also popped for child porn.
And then they ran some article
in a a paper
in the Columbus Dispatch. And I think I
think Wexner bought the paper and the
article doesn't exist anymore.
But there are there is something to
suggest
that that happened
that the second guy who had Epstein's
job
also got popped for that. It almost
makes it seem like
that's part of it.
my guess. I don't know. These people are
very ligious.
So, I gotta be careful about saying
things that are not substantiated as my
producer furiously tries to search for
this because we're literally about to be
sued and killed. We're literally about
to be sued and
we're both about to be sued and killed.
And I didn't even learn this at the
dinner. I learned this um somewhere
else.
I was at Cold Stone Crearyy and someone
said that. Someone said that. They said,
"Did you know this?" And I said,
"Interesting."
So I don't I What do you want me to say?
This Les Wexter fellow I I feel like is
shady. My guess
don't know, but my guess would be that
he's a shady individual. Can we do a
little image? Let's do a Google image.
Just a Google image.
Just an image.
Get up that one in the suit. That one's
the one I like with the bow tie.
Second row to the right.
All the way to the right.
Make that big. That's the essence of the
man.
You got to find a photo. It's the
essence of the man.
He knows things.
He's got a face of a guy that's knows a
few things.
But I told people, I said, "You you you
have to
you have to fire Pam Bondi.
You have to have Just Lane Maxwell
testify.
If there's if there's nothing there, you
got to release all the documents that
you have.
Otherwise, it's going to be a problem.
Now, listen, a lot of people that were
on that island are dead. A lot of them
are 80. A lot of them are probably
living in other countries. It's not, you
know, the perp walk that you want to see
happen is probably not going to happen.
Sorry. That doesn't mean that there
aren't some people that are very guilty
that could face justice and should. It
means that you're not going to get
everybody who's ever done anything on
that island because a lot of them are
probably dead. They're dying by the
minute.
So,
in in conclusion
to that, we we have more to say about
it.
Certainly, they're now coming to Hill.
You know, Dick Durban, who's a Democrat,
the Democrats are running with this, as
you would.
Bondi pressured a thousand FBI personnel
to comb through tens of thousands of
documents related to Epstein and flag
any mention of Trump. This is from The
Hill. Durban made the explosive
allegations in letters he sent Friday to
Bondi Cash Patel and Dan Banino seeking
more information about the
administration handling of files related
to Epstein and asking why senior
officials were allegedly focused on
looking for documents connecting Trump
to Epstein.
Citing information my office received,
Durban said Bondi pressured the FBI to
put approximately a thousand people in
its information management division on
24-hour shifts to review about a 100,000
Epstein related records as part of a
broader effort to release documents
publicly by what Durban called an
arbitrarily short deadline.
They were instructed to flag any records
in which Trump was mentioned, said
Durban. Now, the Wall Street Journal
released this article where Trump wrote
a letter to Epstein for his birthday and
it's some type of letter that uh you
know Epstein's friend sent him body
letters for his 50th birthday. Body
meaning like salacious and inappropriate
and Donald Trump wrote one. Get up the
Trump letter and let's read that. But
again, Trump's saying it didn't happen
and it it's fake and it's not real.
The only way you get ahead of this is if
you fire
Bondi
number one. I'd like to see Bondi and
Cash. I don't know anything about Bino,
but again, if if all three of them, you
know, this is the biggest bungling of
anything ever.
Remember when they had these morons go
out with these binders? Epstein files
phase one. What the [__] were they
thinking?
So, it looks really bad. And if they
want it to look less bad, and I don't
know how bad it is,
but and I don't think the top people
know how bad it is, to be honest. I
don't think people know. I don't know.
And a lot of people that I talked to
don't know.
There's a belief that it's not as bad as
certain people think and it might be
worse than what other people think. It's
somewhere there. It isn't clear how the
letter with Trump's signature was
prepared. Inside the outline of the
naked woman was a typewritten note
styled as an imaginary conversation
between Trump and Epstein written in the
third person voiceover. There must be
more to life than having everything. The
note began. Donald, yes there is, but I
won't tell you what it is. Jeffrey, nor
will I since I also know what it is.
Donald, we have certain things in
common. Jeffrey. Jeffrey. Yes, we do.
Come to think of it, Donald. Enigmas
never age. Have you noticed that,
Jeffrey? As a matter of fact, it was
clear to me the last time I saw you,
Donald, a pal is a wonderful thing.
Happy birthday, and may every day be
another wonderful secret.
Well,
if that's Trump, not ideal, certainly in
hindsight,
um, you got to release everything you've
got.
You He's supposedly suing Murdoch. He's
suing the Wall Street Journal. You have
to release everything you got. You are
you're you're in a scandal that's about
to engulf your presidency that may
already be engulfing the presidency.
And if you do not release everything you
have right now and get rid of the
attorney general because she is either a
not communicating or b lying,
she's either incompetent or or she's
untruthful.
She's not truthful. Is untruthful one of
the things you can say?
I'm asking. You don't know. You don't
know if untruthful is something you can
say? I don't know that.
>> Do you know that?
>> Yes.
>> Can you say untruthful?
>> Yeah.
>> Or not truthful?
>> You can say untruthful.
>> I was right.
But she's got to go. Pam Bondi's got to
go. She's got to go back to Florida and
prosecute people that, you know, are
misbehaving on jet skis. She's got to
get out.
And you got to bring in Megan Kelly.
Truly, you have to bring in Megan Kelly
to be the attorney general of America.
That's it. That's it. No more nonsense.
You can't bring in just TV people. You
got to bring in good TV people.
Ke Patel, these people are like people
who failed at having podcasts.
They would have been mean if they had
talent. They're running the FBI because
they're shot.
These are people that were like hyping
up Q drops on 4chan and leading retards
in every [__] direction thinking that
Hillary was going to GMO and now they're
running the FBI and whether they're in
on it or the deep state is closlining
them. They got to get the [__] out of
there and start a podcast. Half of that
administration needs to start a podcast.
Pam Bondi, I will email you the mics to
buy. You're out. It's time to go.
It's time to go. They took people who
had podcasts and put them in control of
the government. So, either they're
compromised or the [__] factions of
the deep state are are [__]
shoveling [__] on these people at an
amazing pace because they're incapable
of delivering anything. They They appear
to be fools when they go on a show. They
appear to be a fool.
No one likes a fool unless the fool is
aiming to be a fool. Someone with wacky
glasses, something like that. But if if
you are somebody who is running the FBI
and you can't articulate a clear
sentence, you have to go.
I don't care if you're loyal.
You've lost the trust of the voters. You
must go. They got a clean house over
there. Fire a lot of people.
You have to fire a lot of people. I know
you don't like that. Now, here's the
good news. The guy in charge likes
firing.
Some would say he owns that term. You're
fired. He probably tried to copyright
it.
You got to release everything you've got
and fire these people unless it's it's
just not going to go well.
It's not going to go well. It's a
blackmail operation. We know it. He was
laundering money. We know that. He made
money disappear. That was probably his
main thing.
Sax was a part of it. He had he had lots
of powerful people. He had information
on a lot of powerful people and he
allowed intelligence agencies
to access that information.
CIA, MI6, MSAD, all these different
intelligence agencies are largely crime
syndicates who have existing
relationships with each other. They work
with each other and then one will
recruit somebody and then someone's a
double agent and a triple agent. You got
to release everything you have. That
world is shadowy and murky. And I don't
know if the information I got was true.
What the [__] do I know? I'm sitting
there at a dinner. I'm telling you that
is what is believed by people in the
administration who they themselves may
be getting lied to. I don't know. They
don't know.
Everyone makes fun of me for going, "Oh,
you said that they would be killed
genuinely at the dinner it came up." No
one believes the crooks thing. No one
believes that. No one believes that.
that this is just a random kid that had
no prior relationship to anybody and he
was just able to fly a drone over a
rally and climb on a thing. No one
believes that.
No one believes Epstein killed himself.
People believe he was murdered or he was
switched out
and he's now a a server at Mitchell's
Ocean Club in in Ohio in Columbus,
which is the original restaurant that
started Ocean Prime. It's a great
restaurant. And Cameron Mitchell, the
owner of that, wrote a book called It
doesn't. The answer is yes. Doesn't
matter what the question is. And that
was about restaurants hopefully. But the
point is, we don't know what's going on.
So, you have to release everything.
A little bit of grand jury testimony is
not going to do it.
I told everyone at the dinner, I said,
"It's it looks very bad." And they they
all knew that.
They all knew that this is Trump's tweet
based on the ridiculous amount of
publicity given to the Jeff Jeffrey
Epstein. And I've asked attorney general
Pam Bondi to produce any and all
pertinent grand jury testimony subject
to court approval. This scam perpetuated
by the Democrat should end right now.
Trump believes that connecting him to
Epstein is a Democrat scam, hoax,
whatever. Prove it. You got to release
everything. I know it'll be
uncomfortable. It's going to be
uncomfortable to release all the things.
It's just an uncomfortable reality.
Sometimes you are friends with someone
and they're a human trafficker. That's
what it is to be rich. Explain that to
people.
Tell them that what it is to be rich is
to be best friends sometimes with a
human trafficker satanic pedophile. You
don't even know it. You just know that
you both like boats. To be rich is to be
friends with people who are implicated
in the murders of their wives,
the trafficking of children,
coups,
drug running, narco trafficking, arms
dealing,
false flag operations. It's this is what
it is to be rich. It's not for everyone.
I've always said that. I've always said
it's not for everyone.
To be rich is not to be around school
teachers,
good people who teach the kids all day.
Here, here's your pass out these folders
of your homework. That's not what it is.
I have a little bit of money now. Not
even a lot. I haven't spoke to a
firefighter in six years. I don't even
know where they are. Cops, firefighters,
teachers. Who are these people? I go to
dinner with people I'm pretty sure want
to kill me.
They always choose a nice restaurant.
That's where I go and it's near my home.
But I I'm friends with people now I'm
pretty sure are on an assignment to kill
me. Truly, it's what happens when you
have a little bit of money. I don't even
have a lot of money. But a little bit of
money, unfortunately, you get a set of
friends and they're all predominantly
morally questionable and you don't know
them. Rich people are private.
The middle class isn't. The middle class
is always telling you about the fights
they've had with their husband or wife.
They're fat kids that won't get to get
it together. Their daughter who's pissed
them off because she hasn't filled out
her college application. Well, we're not
going to tour the school for their she
doesn't get on it. They're always
vomiting their lives to you. But the
rich are quiet. They they quietly
drowning the chef in the Martha's
Vineyard pond. Get in the [__] water
quietly. They don't bring it up.
Explain that to people, Donald. go out
and say to them sometimes you just end
up best friends with someone who's
trafficking children and it's because
you both you know they're fun. Here's
the thing with human traffickers.
They're fun. Are you telling me you
don't think Just Lane Maxwell was fun?
There's not one photo of Just Lane
Maxwell where she doesn't look like the
funnest person that's [__] ever
lived. And that doesn't make me happy. I
don't like that.
Yeah, she's a satanic pedophile. I get
it. She's evil. They're both evil.
Sometimes rich people are evil. Duh.
She's massaging his feet on a plane. The
[__] played her position. She was fun.
The woman was fun. Look at how relaxed
he looks. The point is
you got to explain to people that this
is unfortunately
part of it's the the people at the top
of society are in they're into [__] and
they're involved in [__]
But you got to show everyone that you're
not involved in it. So you got to
release it. You can be at a party with
someone. You can shake a hand. You can
hang out with someone even. But but you
need to prove that you are not
in any way associated with this part of
this man.
Get that a pick away of the foot,
please. And her. You have to show the
world that
you can say, "I made an oopsie.
I made an oopsie.
You can say that.
I took a ride on a plane that I
shouldn't have been. I thought he was
just a whack.
But he was a wacko.
He was a silly Billy.
Maybe that's what you say. Go. He was a
silly Billy.
He was a daffy duck.
But you got to show people you weren't
raping children. That's what you have to
show people.
I don't even care if he laundered a
little bit of the money. No one does. No
one does. Donald, if that's what you're
worried about, no one cares.
It's okay
if he laundered some of your even a lot
of your money. If he laundered a lot of
your money that because that's not what
people are thinking.
God, it would be fun if you if if he
just laundered some of your goddamn
money. Just say that. Say that. Say, "I
got a casino as a cash business. He
laundered some money." Say it. Say it
now. That's not impeachable. Who cares?
He laundered some money. Godamn it. Say
that, please. We want it to be that.
That's what people want it to be.
I of course a lot of people don't want
it to be that, but I don't want Clinton
[__] the kids either, even though
that's not I, you know, there's a
there's a [__] breadcrumb trail that
isn't ideal,
but I don't want any of our presidents
to be having sex with children. This is
not my idea of a good time. Now, that
unfortunately seems to be uh more than
likely something that has happened. So,
you need to prove that you did not do
that.
Please God, just say he laundered the
money.
He He became my friend because he knew
how to make large sums of money
disappear. I didn't want to pay taxes. I
didn't want to pay these taxes.
Um, people are okay with that. People
will be okay with that.
Just say you stole money.
Jesus, please just come out and say, "I
stole my He stole the money with me.
I was just He was laundering my money. I
wasn't [__] the kids. He was
laundering my money. Scream it. Have a
press conference and go Jeffrey Epstein
laundered my money.
And I And that was wrong. And that was
wrong.
It was wrong what he did with the
laundering of my money. But here's all
the files. I didn't do anything else. It
was just about money.
That would be nice. That would be ideal.
Something's going on. I don't know what
it is.
Something's happening.
The intelligence community
isn't a monolith. They're not any one
thing. So, there's people in the CIA
that do not like Israel, and there are
people that love it.
There is
an opposing there are opposing factions
in all of these places.
People go, "Well, why was Ebstein even
arrested if it's a whole thing?" People
in those agencies, some of them want
justice. Truly, and when they're
presented with a case and there are
witnesses, they do what you should do as
a cop. You arrest the bad guy.
But then when it gets to the legal level
and Alexander Acasta is told, I was told
to not
take it any further with Epstein because
he quote belonged to intelligence.
That's an anonymous quote that Vicky
that someone else said Alexander Aosta
said. It was given to Vicky Ward at
Vanity Fair who you know is a credible
reporter. I don't think she's making
stuff up. She got an anonymous quote.
Get Alexander Acasta. Get him on the
stand.
get him on the stand
because
we know
that something is rotten here. We know
that. And please God, let it be that he
laundered a little bit of your money.
Oh, he laundered my money.
[Music]
I don't [__] the kids.
Come on.
He lo I was a casino guy. We had a lot
of cash.
And he laundered the money. Maybe that's
it.
Huh? We don't know. Lesser of two evils.
Or nothing h or nothing illegal
happened. Even better. He did nothing
illegal. I was friends with him and and
he was he did illegal thing because the
Jeffrey Epste is like they're doing all
these things. He's a Wall Street guy.
And uh but but here's the other thing.
No one knew how he made any of his
money. He had like one client. It was
Adnan Kosigible,
Jamal Kosigible, the guy who the Saudis
killed in that embassy was I think Adnan
Kosogible's brother or
son, but I don't know. He was related to
him in some way. Adnan Kosogi was
Epstein's client. Like Epstein was
supposedly this guy who had
all of this money, the largest residence
in Manhattan, and nobody knew how he got
any of that money. And nobody had ever
worked for him. He didn't have like he
wasn't like Steven Cohen who owns the
Mets who they the show Billions is based
on who has a you know a hedge fund in
Connecticut 72 and there's a bunch of
people that worked there and there's
people that have worked with Steven
Cohen and can talk about Stephen Cohen.
He's a legendary stock trader and
there's articles written about Stephen
Cohen. Every article about Epstein's
like, "Who is he? What's he doing?"
But go to the VH1, see if you can Oh,
yeah. Jeffrey Epste, international money
man of mystery. Terrific guy. Donald
Trump booms from a speakerphone. He's a
lot of fun to be with. And maybe that
was true.
So, this whole thing here, this was an
article from what year?
>> 2002.
>> 2002. They're writing about Jeffrey
Epstein. He's, listen to this, ready?
He's pals with and this is New York
magazine. This is the magazine of the,
you know, chattering class, the smart
set, you know, the bold-faced names, the
glitterati.
He's pals with a pel of Nobel
prizewinning scientist, CEOs like Leslie
Wexner of the limited socialite Gain
Maxwell, even Donald Trump. But it
wasn't until he flew Bill Clinton, Kevin
Space, and Chris Tucker to Africa on his
private Boeing 727 that the world began
to wonder who he is. Jeffrey Epstein,
international moneyman of mystery.
And this is an article and you can all
read it. And it's funny. It's in
hindsight. It's one of the funniest
articles that you'll ever read.
You know, he comes with cash to burn, a
fleet of airplanes, and a keen eye for
the ladies.
That's the first line.
It's a life full of question marks.
Epstein is said to run a 15 billion to
run 15 billion for wealthy clients. Yet,
aside from limited founder Leslie
Wexter, his client list is closely held
secret. A former adult math teacher, he
maintains uh um periopetic salon of
brilliant scientists, yet possesses no
bachelor's degree.
For more than 10 years, he's been linked
to Manhattan London society figure Gain
Maxwell, daughter of the mysteriously
deceased media titan Robert Maxell.
Robert Maxwell. Yet he lives a life of a
bachelor logging six hours a year in his
various planes as he scour the world.
Like it's a lifestyles of the rich and
famous thing. See if you can get on
Instagram. They did VH1 did like the
fabulous life of billionaires.
There used to be these shows on TV by
the way before people were like uh you
know uh in the financial position where
they were considering eating their cat.
They used to watch shows like uh the
fabulous life of you know and it would
just be it's a rage bait but people
would like it back then and you would
just watch really rich people do rich
[__] Let's watch a little bit of this.
This and VH1 has pulled this,
you know, obviously for obvious reasons,
but this was a
uh this was a go to the one that's three
minutes.
And this is something that VH1 had aired
about Jeffrey Epste. And again, it's
unintentionally
hilarious. Now, in hindsight, let's
watch.
In the next hour, we'll tour the hedro
mega homes they're buying with all that
hedge fund cash, but not quite as much
as financier Jeffrey Epstein.
Jeff was a high school math teacher
until he traded his blackboard for the
big board in 1976,
eventually launching his own exclusive
finance firm for billionaire clients.
But he just couldn't keep out of the
classroom. So when he was shopping for a
new house, he bought himself an entire
schoolhouse
and transformed it into the largest
single residence in all of Manhattan at
a whopping 51,000.
>> By the way, pause this for a second.
There's there had to be people who knew
he was a pedophile who saw this and were
like, "This is amazing."
>> You know what I mean? Like there are
people that obviously for this guy's
entire life knew he was a pedophile and
victims of his who were watching VH1 saw
this. Like literally people that he had
victimized
turned on VH1,
you know, to watch, I don't know, a Tony
Braxton music video and they're watching
uh Jeffrey Epste like he couldn't stay
out of the classroom.
He bought himself a whole school.
And there's people that were like,
"Yeah, I know. He raped me in it. Yeah,
I'm uh I'm well aware of that.
>> Square.
>> Oh yeah.
>> The school cost about $20 million and
he's dropped $10 million just renovating
it.
>> It has incredible bells and whistles.
Closed circuit televisions, a heated
sidewalk out front, so the snow melts.
>> But only one man truly rules the Wall
Street skies. Cuz for former school
teacher turned billionaire Jeffrey
Epstein, one private plane won't do.
He's got a small fleet. A Gulfream 4, a
Cessna, and a Boeing 726.
>> Stop for a minute. Do you realize how
important Hollywood is like in just
narratives?
>> You how important it is like that they
no longer have the ability to do this?
It's like you can't just do this without
any push back or without anybody on the
internet challenging what you you what
conclusions you come to.
This is a puff piece going he's a Wall
Street legend. And by the way, no
company, no employees, nobody that has
ever said they worked for the guy. A
couple of journalists are like, "This
isn't adding up." And VH1 just runs this
whole thing where they're like he's a
genius.
This guy is he was a math teacher and
it's like Goodwill Hunting.
He was a math teacher. Now he's a he's a
Wall Street legend. He's a math teacher.
So it's Goodwill Hunting. They didn't
realize it was Goodwill Hunting for
children. But that's what it was. You
had the ability to just project this
image
of a mysterious
guy who had all these connection. And by
the way, that would never work anymore
because we know what mysterious means.
Mysterious means you're just you're
having sex with children on an I. I
mean, there's no By the way, used to be
able to say somebody was mysterious and
it was like some kind of compliment.
You'd be like, "Wow, he's mysterious. We
don't know what he's doing." Now use
that word. You go, "Yeah, keep them away
from my house."
Mystery now is bad. It is bad. Like
celebrities
over because there's no more Mystique.
There's no more mystery. It's like,
yeah, because mystery now means people
think, "Oh, I guess you're having sex
with children. That's mystery. I guess
you're laundering money for a human
trafficking operate." Like, so it's
amazing to me that they're running this
puff piece, this positive,
you know, piece talking about the
glamorous life of this human tra and you
would never know. You'd be sitting on
your couch going because that's what
Wall Street is, by the way, to most
people. Like a lot of finance is fake,
truly. And and most people just believe
that. They're like, "I didn't have the
right connections. I didn't go to the
right schools." They don't even try to
understand this crap. I remember that
during the mortgage crisis when they're
trying to explain credit default swaps
on Fox and they were like, "Well, the
credit defaults and people are like,
"Fuck this. You're all crooks."
Because it's structured finance, lots of
it, is fake. It is largely
uh a a science of what most people would
call outright criminality.
And so when they used to run pieces like
this, nobody would think anything of it.
They'd go, "Yeah, he's just a, you know,
it's a guy on Wall Street and he's
making gobs of money doing god knows
what." But little do they know,
this is actually an evil, cruel,
sadistic monster. And you're talking
about the renovation he's doing to his
house, his schoolhouse
that he's living in in Manhattan. Keep
going.
>> With, of course, an inflight trading
room.
>> He has a Boeing 727. I'm just wondering
now, what do you need a commercial size
airliner for?
>> Believe us, it comes in handy when
you've got powerful friends to fly
around.
When Bill Clinton organized a week-long
tour of Africa in 2002, Jeff gave him a
ride in his personal 727
and took actors Kevin Spacy and Chris
Tucker along for the trip.
>> Now, for former President Clinton, it
was a chance to investigate the problems
of AIDS and Africa. And for Epstein, it
was a chance to hang out with some of
his big shot friends.
>> Jet setting with Bill.
>> I love, by the way, I love the idea of
that. I love the idea of Bill Clinton
and Jeffrey Epstein
gassing up the jet and going to
investigate AIDS in Africa. And it's
just like an amazing
like he's like, "Let me call Jeffrey
Epstein. Let's go. Let's go find out
what this AIDS is about." And then
Spacy's there. But Spacy, by the way,
was like, "Put it all out." Space like,
"I haven't done anything. Put it out.
Put it out."
So, I mean, that that's where we're at.
You can you can scrap this. But I I
watched that and I thought it was so
funny. It was such an interesting
uh thing. Now uh the late show with
Stephen Coar is being cancelled and
people are angry. Trump it's breaking
out that he is suing Murdoch over this
story. People are angry late show with
Stephen Cobear. Supposedly they're
citing a financial decision but people
are saying that it's because Colbear
criticized CBS
uh willing to settle a lawsuit with
Donald Trump.
So people are going out like Bernie
Sanders I think just came out and put
out a if you go to Bernie's Instagram I
believe he put out a statement saying
that this decision is because Steven
Colbear uh had the temerity to criticize
you bring it up Bernie's just doing ads
for Cali Bernie's like do you think
Maxwell will testify go to Khi you can
create your own market CBS asses
billionaire owners pay Trump 16 million
to settle a bogus lawsuit while trying
to sell the network to Sky Dance. Steven
Coar an extraordinary talent. He was and
the most popular late night host. Not
true. It's gutfeld to be honest. I mean,
whatever you think about anything, that
is the truth. Slams the deal. Days
later, he's fired. Do you think this is
a coincidence? No. Here's the thing.
Late night feels like it's on its way
out. And could this have made CBS make
their decision quicker? Sure. Are we
going to have late night shows in five
years? I really don't know. It doesn't
seem like we are. Doesn't seem like
we're three years. There's people that
go on late night. You know who they are.
There's a lot of people that go on late
night. No one really knows who they are.
And so the you know the host is doing
like
banter with someone who the audience
doesn't know who they are and they
they've never seen the show they're on
and no one knows what's happening. So no
one knows what's going on. Not everyone
obviously there's people that people
know but these people come on late night
and the host is like hey
we got the new star Carolina Blue here
you know and they're like give it up for
Jasmine Mitchell Stein
and you know she's the girl will come on
and she'll be like Stephen
such a fan love you and he's like this
show is great no one's heard of the show
no one has heard of the show in the
audience. He's like, "Now, this show,
tell us about the show because it's
amazing. This show you're on, everyone
loves this show. It's called Carolina
Blue." And she's like, "Yeah, it's about
the Blue family and Carolina. They're
super They're super uptight." And then
one summer, everything threatens to be
unraveled by a really wild secret. And
he's like, "And people can't get enough
of this show." And the audience is
sitting there. They don't know what's
happening. The show might as well be
fake. The show might as well not exist.
No one knows who the person is. What did
I call her? Mitchell Stein. What was her
name? What name did I just say? Carmen.
Sarah.
>> Jody.
>> Did I say Jodie?
>> I don't think so. Do you remember what I
said?
>> No.
>> You have a broken brain. But I it
doesn't matter what I said because it
it's every single uh guest on that show
for the most part unless they're like
famous. No one really knows who they are
or what they're doing there.
And he's like, "So this show is amazing.
It's an amazing show and it's on it's on
Hulu Plus, right? That's where it's on."
She's like, "Yeah." So, if you upgrade
your Hulu to Hulu Plus, you can watch
Carolina Blue. And he's like, "Now, the
first season
uh was in 2021,
and season 2 is premiering in 2027,
right?" So, it's a six-year gap. Uh, but
we're revisiting a small beachside town
in Carolina. It no one knows. And the
audience are just sitting there and the
audience are all people that are just in
New York City.
and someone goes see
Colbear and they know who Colbear is and
they know the Ed Sullivan theater and
many of them grew up watching David
Letterman and America's all about
celebrities. That's why people like from
Sweden come here. It's not to eat our
poison uh buckets of uh a poison dough
that we make our bread from. It's
because they they really want to see a
celebrity and they want to see how rich
and fat we all are. That's why they come
here. They got to see America. They got
to see America. How rich are they? How
fat are they? How how amazing is New
York? They want to see a real city, not
like an ancient city or you know what I
mean? Um and their traffickers in Sweden
and stuff, it's like all the royals and
really rich creepy people. It's an A24
movie, but our people that are human
traffickers are like not even hiding.
They're like barely hiding it. So that
that impresses them. They're like
they're rich and fat and they're
pedophiles. Don't even hide it. So, they
come to see all of this uh circus of
America and then they're in the Ed
Sullivan Theater and they're like,
"Who's coming out tonight?" JLo.
And it's like a a comedian with 8700
followers who's on a show that on Amazon
that no one's watched.
And he's like, "So now tell us what it
is was like to grow up
uh as a non you were So now you were
non-binary in Oklahoma.
Tell us about that because that's the
premise of this show, right? the show is
that you're you're non-binary in
Oklahoma, but you're also like one of
the top poker players in the world, but
no one knows you're non-binary from
Oklahoma because it's all online, right?
That's and the people in the audience
are like, "We just want to see
pedophiles or JLo or fat people." We
came to America. It was a long flight.
It was a really long flight. We just
want to see pedophiles, fat people, or
JLo. They want to watch a celebrity just
smack a minority in a face like an
immigrant. That's what they want. They
want they want to see JLo take a garbage
can and and like the the the dream of
someone that comes here from uh
Scandinavian country, one of them. If
you if you come to America from Norway,
your dream is you go to the Ed Sullivan
theater. JLo comes out and then as
you're leaving, you look down an alley
and you see her uh take a garbage can
and there's a little Mexican woman and
JLo puts the can on her. And for
whatever reason, you don't even know
what this woman did to draw the eye of
JLo. But now this little Mexican woman's
got a can on her and she stumbles into
the other building and she and she hits
herself. She like knocks herself out and
she's just rolling with the can and then
JLo gets in gets in the uh black car and
and drives away. That's the dream.
Did Did this lawsuit make them go, "Hey,
let's get rid of
Trump." Uh I mean, let's get rid of Co
Bear because he bothered Trump. Sure. I
don't doubt it.
I don't doubt that that's a possibility.
You know,
Bernie Sanders, go to kshi.com.
Bernie Sanders, does he have his betting
market on Khi?
I'm having fun on there. Will Trump
release any of the Epstein files this
year?
Will just Lane Maxwell testify?
20% chance. I would say it's a little
higher than 20, but not that much
higher. I would say it's a little higher
than 20, but not that much higher. But I
will say this.
I will say this. The people that I spoke
to at the dinner know they have a
problem. They know they have a real
problem. They know that the the the
base is angry. The people that elected
them are angry. They are aware of that.
They get it.
And they know that the best the thing
that needs to happen here is Bondi needs
to be fired
and and Chislain should testify and
people know that you need to release
everything.
You know, they they know that. I don't
know if that's going to happen. And I
don't know if what any of what I was
told is true,
but it does stand to reason that these
tapes are not with Pam Bondi, who's a
buffoon,
and that these tapes, and I'm sure they
exist, are somewhere else, if they
haven't been destroyed. They're either
with they're either with a foreign
intelligence service or our own or both.
There's some kind of dead man switch on
something. I don't know.
I lack the ability to know.
But the people I've speak to, spoken to
did. They get it. They understand that
this is the problem. Not going to say
who they are.
It's not fair to say who they are. I
would I will not say that.
We had a nice time. We had steaks.
We had some salad and it was nice.
I won't say who they are.
I was a little worried
that it was going to be Indian food.
Good luck out there.